(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],[,,,,,,,,,function(e,t,r){},function(e,t,r){},,function(e,t,r){},function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(1),n=r.n(s),a=r(4),c=r.n(a),i=(r(9),r(2)),o=(r(10),r(0));var l=function(e){var t=e.startQuiz;return Object(o.jsxs)(s.Fragment,{children:[Object(o.jsx)("p",{className:"quiz-title flex-center",children:"Welcome to the Javascript Quiz App"}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"flex-center",style:{height:"75vh"},children:Object(o.jsx)("button",{className:"start-quiz-button",onClick:t,children:"Start Quiz"})})]})},d=[{questionText:"What does `` refers to in javascript",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Template literals",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Single quotes",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Double quotes",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Strings",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How to declare an array in javascript",answerOptions:[{answerText:"var arr = [ 1, 2, 3 ]",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"var arr = { 1, 2, 3 }",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"[ 1, 2, 3 ]",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"var arr = ( 1, 2, 3 )",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What is the DOM in javascript",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Data Object Model",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Data Overload Method",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Document Object Model",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Document Object Method",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What is the full form of JS",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Java Script",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Java Scripting",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Java Server",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Java Servlet",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Is Javascript case-sensitive",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"How to write an arrow function in javascript",answerOptions:[{answerText:"func add() {}",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"function add() {}",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"() => {}",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"const add = () => {}",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"What is the value of Boolean(5 > 2)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Is Javascript single-threaded",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Is Javascript asynchronous language",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Why can we access functions in javascript before declaring them",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Functions are partially hoisted",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Functions are fully hoisted",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"We cannot access javascript functions before declaring them",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Because functions are the heart of javascript ;)",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What if we try to give some value to an already defined constant variable",answerOptions:[{answerText:"It will throw the reference error",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"It will throw the not defined error",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"It will throw the type error",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"The constant variable will hold the new value",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Are let and const block scoped",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes, let and const are block scoped",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"No, let and const are function scoped",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How to get the id of an HTML element using javascript DOM",answerOptions:[{answerText:"document.getElementById('Id name')",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"document.getelementbyid('Id name')",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"document.getElementsById('Id name')",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"document.GetElementById('Id name')",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Is Javascript strongly typed language",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Where do we include the javascript file in our html document",answerOptions:[{answerText:"head",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"body",isCorrect:!0}]}],u=(r(12),function(e){var t=e.bgcolor,r=e.completed,s={height:"inherit",width:"".concat(r,"%"),backgroundColor:t,borderRadius:"inherit",textAlign:"right"};return Object(o.jsx)("div",{style:{height:20,width:"30%",backgroundColor:"#fff",borderRadius:20},children:Object(o.jsx)("div",{style:s})})});var x=function(){var e=Object(s.useState)(!0),t=Object(i.a)(e,2),r=t[0],n=t[1],a=Object(s.useState)([]),c=Object(i.a)(a,2),l=c[0],x=c[1],j=Object(s.useState)(0),h=Object(i.a)(j,2),w=h[0],b=h[1],p=Object(s.useState)(0),O=Object(i.a)(p,2),T=O[0],v=O[1],f=Object(s.useState)(!1),m=Object(i.a)(f,2),C=m[0],g=m[1],q=Object(s.useState)(15),y=Object(i.a)(q,2),I=y[0],S=y[1];return Object(s.useEffect)((function(){x(d),n(!1)})),Object(s.useEffect)((function(){var e=setInterval((function(){S(I-1)}),1e3);return 14===w&&0===I&&g(!0),0===I&&(clearInterval(e),S(15),b(w+1)),function(){return clearInterval(e)}}),[I]),Object(o.jsx)(s.Fragment,{children:C?Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"flex-center",style:{height:"100vh"},children:Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"results-page flex-column",children:[Object(o.jsx)("h1",{children:"Results Page"}),Object(o.jsxs)("p",{children:["You scored",Object(o.jsx)("span",{style:{fontSize:"50px",padding:"10px"},children:T}),"out of",Object(o.jsx)("span",{style:{fontSize:"50px",padding:"10px"},children:"15"})]}),0===T?Object(o.jsx)("p",{children:"Better luck next time :(("}):T<=10?Object(o.jsx)("p",{children:"Keep learning!! You can do a lot better:)"}):T>=10?Object(o.jsx)("p",{children:"Good job!! You are on a path to becoming a great developer one day :))"}):15===T?Object(o.jsx)("p",{children:"Great job!! You truly are a javascript ninja ;)))"}):""]})}):Object(o.jsxs)(s.Fragment,{children:[Object(o.jsx)("p",{className:"quiz-title flex-center",children:"Welcome to the Javascript Quiz App"}),Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex-center progress-bar",children:[Object(o.jsxs)("span",{className:"progress-bar-text",children:["Question: ",w+1,"/15"]}),Object(o.jsx)(u,{bgcolor:"rgba(0, 0, 175, 0.6)",completed:w/15*100})]}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"flex-center",children:!r&&l.length>0?Object(o.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"flex-center",style:{margin:"10px"},children:Object(o.jsxs)("p",{className:"flex-center time-left",children:["Time Left: ",I," sec"]})}),Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-container",children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"individual-question flex-center",children:l[w].questionText}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"answers",children:l[w].answerOptions.map((function(e){return e?Object(o.jsx)("button",{className:"individual-answer",onClick:function(t){!function(e){!0===e&&v(T+1);var t=w+1;S(15),t<15?b(t):g(!0)}(e.isCorrect)},children:e.answerText}):null}))})]})]}):Object(o.jsx)("div",{children:" Loading "})})]})})};var j=function(){var e=Object(s.useState)(!0),t=Object(i.a)(e,2),r=t[0],n=t[1];return Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"App",children:r?Object(o.jsx)(l,{startQuiz:function(){n(!1)}}):Object(o.jsx)(x,{})})},h=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,14)).then((function(t){var r=t.getCLS,s=t.getFID,n=t.getFCP,a=t.getLCP,c=t.getTTFB;r(e),s(e),n(e),a(e),c(e)}))};c.a.render(Object(o.jsx)(n.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(o.jsx)(j,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),h()}],[[13,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.65216e88.chunk.js.map